<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-10-13T16:11:58+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Abhay Sibal</title><subtitle>Thinker. Learner. Developer.</subtitle><author><name>Abhay Sibal</name></author><entry><title type="html">Hello World - From Abhay !</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/13/hello-world.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello World - From Abhay !" /><published>2018-10-13T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2018-10-13T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/10/13/hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/13/hello-world.html">&lt;p&gt;Connecting my blog to the vast digital ocean of the World Wide Web!
I haven’t been a blogger or a notes-for-everything person ever :),  but this blog represents my first push towards organizing and sharing things that I find interesting, things that I feel are worth to spend time, effort and energy to pursue and explore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-me&quot;&gt;About me&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;My interests are mostly concentrated around Machine Learning, Natural Language Processing, Digital Image Processing and Software Architecture Design.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I’ve worked on multiple projects that used Deep Learning and ML techniques for Automatic Text Summarization and identifying Network Security Vulnerabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In my profession as a Software Developer I’ve worked on both client side and server side technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I love to code in Python and C++(11/14) (in that order) and have a fair bit of experience of working in Java and SQL.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I’ve worked as a developer at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/company/walmart-labs-india/&quot;&gt;WalmartLabs, Bangalore&lt;/a&gt; and right now I am working at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/company/adobe/?originalSubdomain=in&quot;&gt;Adobe, Noida&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-this-blog&quot;&gt;About this blog&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I plan to update this blog regularly about technological developments in the field of Computer Science and my attempts at making something out of them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Abhay Sibal</name></author><summary type="html">Connecting my blog to the vast digital ocean of the World Wide Web! I haven’t been a blogger or a notes-for-everything person ever :), but this blog represents my first push towards organizing and sharing things that I find interesting, things that I feel are worth to spend time, effort and energy to pursue and explore. About me My interests are mostly concentrated around Machine Learning, Natural Language Processing, Digital Image Processing and Software Architecture Design. I’ve worked on multiple projects that used Deep Learning and ML techniques for Automatic Text Summarization and identifying Network Security Vulnerabilities. In my profession as a Software Developer I’ve worked on both client side and server side technologies. I love to code in Python and C++(11/14) (in that order) and have a fair bit of experience of working in Java and SQL. I’ve worked as a developer at WalmartLabs, Bangalore and right now I am working at Adobe, Noida. About this blog I plan to update this blog regularly about technological developments in the field of Computer Science and my attempts at making something out of them.</summary></entry></feed>